Crow for MMD
-----------------
●Read and agree with ALL terms of use written in this txt file before using this MikuMikuDance Model Data. If you do not agree with all terms of use, or if you do not understand any part of this terms of use txt file, you are NOT allowed to use this MikuMikuDance Model Data.

●Private Trading and Public Trading of this MMD Model Data is NOT allowed.

●Do not use this MMD Model for works which include obscene, grotesque, &/or violent content.

●Although you are allowed to edit this MMD Model Data, you may NOT 
distribute that MMD Model Data to other users.

●You are NOT permitted to sell this MMD Model data in ANY format, whether digital or in print. This MMD Model data may only be used for non-profit purposes. Do not use this MMD Model data for commercial purposes.

●If you find this MMD Model Data re-distributed by anyone other than me "troche" on a NON-JAPANESE website, I would greatly appreciate it if you could ask them to delete it.

---------------
Please use this MMD Model Data at your own risk. I can not be held liable or responsible for any damages caused by using this data.

2018.06.06 troche
t0r0tmmd@gmail.com